Contacts

- **4** 617-750-2160 malorse@comcast.net
- ₩www.github.com
- <u>www.portfolio.com</u>
- Boston, MA 02132

Skills: JavaScript HTML CSS SASS Node.js React Ruby on Rails SQL

Part-Time Work: Live Event Production 2009-2018 **BCN Productions** IATSE Local 11 Camera operation **Event Coordination** Non-linear editing Audio Engineering Stage Hand/ Carpenter **Production Assistant** Camera operator Harvard University live sporting events. Camera Operator Boston Cannons and Boston Breakers

Education:

Wentworth Institute of Technology University of Massachusetts at Amherst **Boston Latin School?**

Geoffrey Morse

Junior Software Developer

Portfolio

Project1 Something Fabulous Project2 Something More Fabulous

Project3 Something Fabulous Project4 Something Fabulous

Experience

General Assembly Boston, MA 2019-present

Software Engineer Graduate

- Finished 12 week, 500+ hour immersive program
- Completed four projects
- Javascript, AJAX, cURL, Node.is, React, HTML, CSS, SASS, Ruby on Rails, SQL, JSON,

Construction Supervisor

2006-2019

- Liaise with clients, designers and architects on renovation remodels
- Project budgeting and management
- Reading and relaying blue prints.
- Code evaluation
- Responsible for day to day operations of building sites.
- Adjusted schedules needed to meet all project deadlines.
- Managing and scheduling sub-contractors.
- Managing, directing and training employees.

Lead Finish Carpenter

2000-2006

- Start to finish home construction
- Planning and designing finish carpentry projects.
- Responsible for completion of carpentry projects.
- Interacting with clients.
- Use of power tools and hand tools.

Summary

MA Construction Supervisors License Co-founder of Prophetless Productions. Booked and promoted live music events in Boston.

Independent film work. List of projects I worked on? I don't really feel a need to include this type of stuff.